<resources>
    <array name="questions">
        <item>Where can you go?</item>
        <item>Where and how to pick up and return the car?</item>
        <item>How do you pay for a reserved car?</item>
        <item>Do I need to pay for the delivery of the car?</item>
        <item>Is daily mileage limited?</item>
        <item>Do you have a child seat?</item>
        <item>Do I need to pay a deposit?</item>
        <item>Do I need to wash my car before returning it?</item>
        <item>How do you rent a car?</item>
        <item>What do you need to rent a car?</item>
        <item>Do I need to pay for gasoline?</item>
        <item>Do you provide reporting?</item>
        <item>Do you have car insurance?</item>
        <item>Are the cars covered, like car sharing?</item>
        <item>What are the fines for failure to comply with conditions or violation of traffic
            rules?
        </item>
        <item>Is it possible to transfer a car to another person?</item>
        <item>What to do if the car breaks down?</item>
        <item>If the car was towed?</item>
        <item>Is it possible to rent a car with pets?</item>
        <item>What to do if you forgot things in the car?</item>
    </array>
    <array name="answers">
        <item>There are no restrictions on travel within the Siberian Federal District. Intersection
            The Siberian Federal District, as well as the borders of the Russian Federation, is
            agreed with the manager.
        </item>
        <item>The car is provided in a clean condition, with a full tank of fuel and completely
            ready for
            travel at the point of issue or delivered to the desired location. Returned in the same
            form and with
            the same amount of fuel in a place convenient for you, but according to preliminary
            agreements.
        </item>
        <item>You can pay for the reserved car using a credit card or cash
            or bank transfer, payment is made for the entire period of car rental. If the car
            returns earlier than the specified period, we will recalculate, and only
            time of use.
        </item>
        <item>If you need a car delivery in the city, then you pay for it separately at
            following tariffs:
            500 – night time from the office (from 20:00 to 9:00)
            1000 – daytime, anywhere in the city (from 9:00 to 20:00)
            2000 – night time, anywhere in the city (from 20:00 to 9:00)

            When renting for 7 days or more, delivery is free!
        </item>
        <item><![CDATA[There is a daily mileage limit of 200 km, which is included in the rental price. You
            You can exceed this limit, in which case overmileage is calculated at the rate of 5
            rubles/km
            (economy), 10 rubles/km (comfort and premium).]]>
        </item>
        <item>Yes, we can provide you with a child seat and other additional equipment -
            for free. Before renting, you must first clarify which equipment you will need.
            required.
        </item>
        <item><![CDATA[Yes, a deposit is required. The deposit is a guarantee of the tenant\'s performance of
            the contract.
            The security deposit is not part of the rental price and is paid separately. Collateral
            is a fixed amount of money - auto section \"Economy\" - 5,000 rubles, auto
            sections \"Comfort\" and \"Premium\" - 10,000 rubles. Personal belongings, passport, and
            other documents
            are not collateral. We return the deposit to you at the time of handing over the car and
            signing the certificate.
            reception/transmission, so you don’t have to wait.]]>
        </item>
        <item>No, if the car is provided in a clean condition.
            Yes, washing is paid separately - 1,000 rubles.

            In what case does the client pay for the car wash:
            1. The car is dirty outside and inside;
            2. The car is clean on the outside, but dirty on the inside (rugs, crumbs, stains);
            3. The car is clean inside, but dirty outside (sills, wheels, individual parts
            car);
            4. The car is covered in sand or dust.

            Weather conditions are not a condition for non-fulfillment of contractual obligations
            regarding
            car washes.

            If at the time of booking the car is in a dirty condition, we offer you
            choose what type of car to rent in order to save your money on
            washing

            Emergency car delivery (30 – 90 minutes) does not guarantee a clean car delivery
            form, because It takes at least 2 hours to wash a car. Therefore, we recommend booking
            car in advance.
        </item>
        <item>Renting a car occurs in several stages:

            1. You choose the car you like;
            2. Familiarize yourself with the terms of car rental on the website, or consult with
            manager by phone or messenger;
            3. Send the documents for verification by the security service. This stage takes no more
            20 minutes;
            4. The manager confirms the reservation with a reply message.

            At the appointed date and time we meet with you to sign the contract and transfer
            selected car. The conclusion of a contract is possible only if the client has
            Passport and driver\'s license in hand.
        </item>
        <item>Age of 22 years, driver\'s license category B with at least 2 years of experience and
            general civil passport of the Russian Federation.
        </item>
        <item>You refuel the car yourself, only with AI-95 gasoline. The car is delivered with
            the amount of fuel remaining after previous use.
            Accordingly, the car must be returned at the same level. If there is fuel in the tank
            less than it was when the car was handed over to you, then payment is made at the rate
            of 50
            rubles - one liter. A car with a full tank is provided exclusively upon the client\'s
            request.
        </item>
        <item>Yes, a complete package of documents with all receipts.</item>
        <item>Cars are insured by the MTPL policy.

            If the accident occurred through no fault of yours, and all certificates from the scene
            of the accident are provided - the amount
            responsibility is zero.

            If the accident occurred due to the fault of the client, then responsibility for
            compensation lies with
            per client. If it is impossible to prove the guilt of a third party, liability
            also falls on the client.
        </item>
        <item>No, the cars are not branded.</item>
        <item><![CDATA[Fines for traffic violations are paid by the client. Once the fine is received by us,
            manager we will send you information about him. You only need to transfer the fine
            amount via
            landlord\'s details.

            Fine for smoking in the cabin – 5000
            Fine for late payment for car renewal – 1000 rubles/day
            Fine for loss of documents – 10,000 rubles/unit
            Fine for loss of key/alarm – 10,000 rubles/unit]]>
        </item>
        <item>Yes, if it meets the requirements of the Vodimobil rental terms. Agreement for the
            second
            driver - 300 rubles.
        </item>
        <item>In case of an accident or any damage to the car, call us and report
            happened: we will tell you how to act in this situation. If an accident occurs
            not through your fault, and all certificates from the scene of the accident are provided
            - the amount of liability is equal to
            zero.
        </item>
        <item>Contact support by phone or write to us on social media. networks and us
            We\`ll tell you how to act and what to do in such a situation.
        </item>
        <item>Unfortunately, this option is not available when renting.</item>
        <item>Write or call us, we will do our best to return your items.</item>
    </array>
</resources>
